touricoholidays.com 2017-03-03

# Privacy Policy - TouricoHolidays.comTouricoHolidays.com

Tourico Holidays, a brand of Travel Holdings, Inc. is committed to maintain security and confidentiality of the personal information gathered and used on the [www.touricoholidays.com](http://www.touricoholidays.com/) website (“hereinafter the Website”). This Privacy Statement covers [www.touricoholidays.com](http://www.touricoholidays.com/).

## Information Collected

TouricoHolidays.com collects information that you voluntarily provide to us on the Website. The types of personal identifying information (â€œPIIâ€) that may be collected on the Website are customer name, names of companion travelers, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number(s), date of birth, passport information, credit card and payment information and weight. Non-personal data that you voluntarily provide to us may be collected on the Website during your usage of the site.

Children and individuals under 18 years of age are not permitted to register or make purchases on our site.

## Information Use

TouricoHolidays.com gathers, stores, and processes the PII in order to respond to requests for travel products and services and to improve our Website and service. TouricoHolidays.com may share your information with its authorized technology, marketing and service providers. However, TouricoHolidays.com does not sell, share, rent, or trade personal information to third parties for promotional purposes. The suppliers of travel inventory (hotels, cruise lines, etc.) that receive your information may have privacy policies that are different than this Privacy Policy. Our credit card processing uses your PII solely to facilitate the completion of your travel booking.

We may share your information you provide, including PII, with third parties in a legal proceeding, when there is reasonable to believe that illegal or fraudulent activity has or may occur, and/or in certain corporate transactions provided the recipients of the data in these transactions are contractually obligated to abide by this or a similar Privacy Policy.

Non-personal information may be linked to your PII and provided to authorized, third parties to improve our Website and service. These third parties may be located outside the USA.

TouricoHolidays.com may automatically collect statistics about your visit to our Website when you visit the Website without registering. This information does not identify you as an individual and it is intended to gather information about your visit to our Website. The types of information that may be collected is your IP address, pages visited on the Website, addresses of websites visited that are linked to our Website or which we have a relationship, and similar information. This information is collected through the use of tracking technologies such as log files and web beacons.

## Option To Control Information

PII does not have to be revealed when you visit the Website. Nevertheless, TouricoHolidays.com may collect data about your use of the Website; this data will be anonymous and will not be linked to any PII unless that information is provided voluntarily. This information is collected to help us improve our Website and service.

TouricoHolidays.com may place a â€œcookieâ€ or computer file on your computer and/or use other technologies to enable us to recognize you when you visit our site again and to measure the effectiveness of our Website. You may instruct your computer not to accept cookies. Our cookies are linked to PII. Additionally, we use a third- party tracking service that uses cookies to track non-PII about visitors to our site.

PII that you voluntarily provide to TouricoHolidays.com when you register with us can be edited or removed by accessing the Member section on our Website by logging into â€œMy Accountâ€ and changing your personally identifying information. We may retain travel records for six (6) months after a request for removal to ensure that the any existing travel arrangements are concluded and/or if we are legally required to retain the records. If you provide TouricoHolidays.com with additional PII, such as travel provider membership numbers or ticketing preferences, we may retain that information. This information may be edited or removed, as well. You may not be able to edit or remove data or information we collect from third parties. You can also send an email to [webmaster@travelholdings.com](mailto:webmaster@travelholdings.com) to have your PII changed.

## Communications From The Site And How To Opt-out

You will receive transaction or service related communications from the Website when you purchase travel products and services through our Website. Additionally, you will receive promotional communications from us if you choose to receive these communications.

You may choose at any time during the registration process to â€œopt-outâ€ and choose not to receive promotional communications that TouricoHolidays.com feels may interest you. You may choose to unsubscribe and not receive future promotional communications by accessing the unsubscribe link on an email received by TouricoHolidays.com. You can also â€œopt-outâ€ of receiving these newsletters by logging into your account and â€œopting-outâ€ of receiving these newsletters.

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friendâ€™s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. TouricoHolidays.com does not store this information.

## Blogs And Testimonials

If you comment to a blog or post a testimonial on this Website, you should be aware that any PII you submit can be read, collected, or used by other users on these forums, and the PII can be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for and will not protect the privacy of the PII you choose to submit in these forums.  
Service Providers

We use third parties to provide credit card processing, email services, web-analytics, and live-chat services on our Website. When you sign up for these services, we will share your PII as necessary for the third party to provide the services. These third parties are prohibited from using your PII for any other purpose. We also have Widgets on this Website which support functions that require that you to disclose certain PII depending on your choice of participation. This information is collected in many different ways such as: forms, surveys, contests, forums, subscribing or unsubscribing to mailings and correcting or updating personally identifiable information and are only used for the purpose in which they were collected.

## Security And Confidentiality

The security of your PII is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the PII submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

When you click on any links on our Website, you leave our Website and enter the website of a third party. Your visit to these third party websites are governed by the privacy and security policies, if any, of those third party sites. TouricoHolidays.com is not responsible for security and confidentiality of your information on third party sites.

We reserve the right to disclose your PII as required by law, when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. In addition, TouricoHolidays.com may disclose certain information in cases of fraud or abuse of the Website.

## Changes To This Privacy Statement

Changes to this Privacy Statement may be made from time to time. If any change is unacceptable to you, you may edit or remove your information subject to the restrictions noted herein and/or change your opt-out preference. TouricoHolidays.com will either inform you by email if you have registered on our Website or by means of a notice on our home page, or another place we deem appropriate, of any material change to this Privacy Statement so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

## Contact Us

If you would like to contact us regarding this Privacy Statement, you can reach us by our mailing address at 220 East Central Parkway, Suite 4000, Altamonte Springs, FL 32701 or by email at [webmaster@travelholdings.com](mailto:webmaster@travelholdings.com).
